For many reasons, the small islands of
Malta that are roughly in the center of
the Mediterranean aren't where you would
initially expect to find a thriving
civilization at. Located roughly 93 km
south of Sicily and about 288 km north
of Libya, the Maltese archipelago
consists of three larger main islands
called Malta, Gozo, and Comino. Along
with several smaller islands that
collectively take up only about 316 sq
km of land. This puts Malta within the
top 10 smallest sovereign countries in
the world today. And to help maybe put
it in a perspective for you, it's less
than half the total size of New York
City.
These small islands are also almost
completely bereft of any resources that
would be useful for a human settlement,
let alone civilization.
There are no mineral or fossil fuel
resources to speak of at all. There is
very limited agricultural land that
would be useful for food production. And
perhaps worst of all, there are
practically zero obvious freshwater
sources, either. There are no permanent
sources of freshwater anywhere on
Malta's surface.
>> [music]
>> No rivers, no lakes, and a dry
environment with scant rainfall that
falls extremely unevenly throughout the
year.
3/4 of Malta's rainfall usually all just
comes during the wet season between
October and March. While the summers are
usually all just completely rain-free
for months at a time. Even worse, the
islands of Malta are basically just
barren limestone rocks protruding out of
the sea. Which means that rainfall on
them rapidly infiltrates the limestone
geology deep underground or runs out to
the sea instead of collecting on the
surface.
These islands are a very difficult to
inhabit set of rocks in the middle of
the salty sea. And yet, Malta is by far
the most densely populated country in
Europe these days regardless. And it's
not even close.
As of 2025, 588,000
people are believed to be living in
Malta. Which gives the country an
incredible population density of 1,838
people per square kilometer. That level
of population density absolutely dwarfs
every single other country within the
EU. The EU's next most [music] densest
country, the Netherlands, is only about
1/4 as dense on average as Malta is. In
fact, Malta's population density is so
significant that it's the fifth most
densely populated country in the entire
world. For mating only behind Monaco,
Singapore, Vatican City, and Bahrain. If
you remove the tiny city states of
Monaco and Vatican City from the
consideration, both of which are only a
tiny fraction of the size of even Malta,
then Malta is really the third most
densely populated non-microstate country
in the world and by far the densest one
in all of Europe.
To put this into a bit more perspective,
Malta has a significantly larger
population than Iceland does. Despite
being way smaller and with substantially
less resources.
Iceland only has a population of 394,000
people compared to Malta's 588,000
people. Despite Iceland being more than
326 times larger than Malta is
geographically.
Life on Malta can feel very crowded and
congested these days despite everything
stacked against it. And what's even more
strange is how all of this is a pretty
recent phenomenon for the country.
Historically, until very recently, Malta
was almost always an emigrant nation
where more people left than came. Over
the course of just a single recent
generation between 1948 and 1967, nearly
a third of Malta's entire population
left the country amidst chronic economic
stagnation and lack of opportunity. And
there are at least two known instances
in Malta's history before then where the
islands have been completely abandoned
and depopulated altogether. So, the big
question that I wanted to ask is why do
so many people live on these tiny,
difficult to inhabit rocks without any
water or useful resources today. How was
Malta able to overcome its seemingly
crippling geographic handicaps to become
the most densely populated country in
Europe today?
To begin answering these questions, we
need to start with a deeper look into
Malta's geography and what makes it more
useful and desirable than its lack of
resources and barriers to settlement
when initially suggest.
Malta's value has never been about what
could be extracted from the island, but
what could be controlled from the
island. Malta is arguably the single
most important geo-strategic location
for any power to control in order to
dominate the Mediterranean Sea other
than maybe the Strait of Gibraltar and
the Sea of Marmara and in more modern
times the Suez Canal.
It sits almost precisely in the dead
center of the Mediterranean near one of
the seas most important geographic
funnels.
Historically, before the creation of the
Suez Canal, the only way for ships to
travel between the western and eastern
halves of the Mediterranean was either
to the north or south of Sicily. Through
either the very narrow Strait of Messina
in the north between Sicily and the
Italian mainland or through the larger
gap between Sicily and modern-day
Tunisia.
And Malta is the most strategically
placed landmass to influence and project
power into that larger southern passage
from.
A power base placed in Malta could most
easily observe, protect, raid, or
threaten shipping moving between the two
halves of the Mediterranean. And that
alone made the possession of Malta
strategically valuable.
Malta also sits in the middle of Europe
and North Africa, which has always made
it strategically useful for powers
moving in both directions. And even
better, the main island of Malta itself
also just happens to possess one of the
finest natural harbors in the entire
Mediterranean as well.
The eastern side of Malta contains both
the Grand Harbor and the Marsamxett
Harbor separated by the large peninsula
in between them where the fortified city
of Valletta was eventually built in the
16th century.
These harbors are deep, sheltered,
extensive, and also surrounded by easily
defensible terrain. The Grand Harbor, in
particular, has all of these narrow
peninsulas and inlets that can be
covered by forts and artillery from
multiple angles of defense, which make
it extremely difficult for any outside
attacker to just simply sail themselves
into the harbor and get away with it.
And this [music] excellent harbor is
also on that very strategically
well-placed island in the center of the
Mediterranean at the entrance to that
passage between Sicily and Tunisia.
A fleet parked in this harbor around
Valletta in Malta could have an
easy-to-defend base to operate
throughout the entire Mediterranean
from, as well as an outpost to control
the movement of trade and enemy naval
forces from passing between both halves
of the Mediterranean, too.
It is basically a pre-made naval
fortress in the heart of the
Mediterranean. And that has made it an
extremely attractive place to be
controlled by empires for thousands of
years now.
Throughout ancient and medieval history,
the island was controlled at various
different times by the Phoenicians,
Carthaginians, Romans, Normans, Arabs,
and Spanish for this very reason. But
its strategic importance reached an
all-time high during the 16th century
when it became a major target of
conquest by the Ottoman Empire. The
Knights Hospitaller, or the Knights of
St. John, was granted sovereignty by the
Holy Roman Empire to rule over Malta in
1530 and to defend it against the
expanding Ottomans.
The Knights were able to use Malta as a
heavily militarized outpost in the
center of the Mediterranean to raid
Ottoman shipping from and to block any
Ottoman expansion from reaching into the
western Mediterranean or southern Italy.
So, naturally, the Ottomans came to view
Malta as a major obstacle to their
expansion. And so, in 1565, they sent an
armada with tens of thousands of men to
try and conquer the island. But despite
outnumbering the defending Knights on
the island by as many as eight to one,
they still failed to overcome Malta's
defenses and nearly the entire attacking
Ottoman force was destroyed.
The control of Malta by the Christian
powers in the 16th century is
effectively what prevented the Ottomans
from expanding into the Western
Mediterranean. And it wouldn't be the
last time that Malta's strategic
geography would affect regional
geopolitics.
Napoleon recognized Malta's strategic
geography during his time as well.
During his expedition to Egypt in 1798,
he managed to succeed where the Ottomans
had failed in conquering Malta from the
knights along the way in order to
protect his own sea lines of
communication and logistics between
Egypt and the French mainland. It didn't
last for long though, because the
islanders rose up in a revolt against
the French quickly thereafter. And then
the British arrived in 1800 to help kick
the French out. And as the British so
often did in their history, they ended
up just staying around afterward and
controlled Malta for the next 164 years
well into the 1960s.
To the British, Malta became one of
their most strategically located
overseas possessions. They transformed
it into a fortress and refueling depot
for the Royal Navy in the center of the
Mediterranean. And it became the
centerpiece in their chain of outposts
on the way to India that ran from the
British mainland through Gibraltar and
Malta and the Suez Canal. And then,
Malta's geo-strategic importance became
extremely acute again during the Second
World War. After Italy entered the war
on the side of the Axis,
British-controlled Malta sat immediately
in between Sicily and Italian-controlled
Libya. Malta was therefore a perfectly
positioned base for the British to use
to attack Axis supply lines running
between Europe and North Africa from. An
unsinkable aircraft carrier and
submarine base deep behind enemy lines
that once again turned Malta into the
object of a relentless campaign to
conquer it. Between 1940 and 1942, the
Axis subjected Malta to a massive
bombing campaign that attempted to
starve the island out through blockade,
while the British went to truly
extraordinary lengths to keep the island
supplied and in the fight. So, Malta's
always been very useful for outside
powers to control or influence from a
strategic perspective, which has always
meant that there have been powerful
empires willing to bankroll the island's
settlement and development. But, the
biggest problem standing in their way
has always been that Malta has basically
zero obvious sources of fresh water or
resources that would be necessary to
sustain that settlement or development.
So, how have the people in Malta managed
to do it anyway? For most of Malta's
history, the strategy of conserving
water was pretty basic. The general rule
was that whenever it rained, as much of
it as possible was to be captured.
Homes, villas, farms, and public
buildings all across the island came to
incorporate underground cisterns. Well,
rain falling on rooftops and courtyards
was channeled towards them.
By the medieval period, most houses in
Malta had these kinds of underground
cisterns built into their architecture.
And while Malta has no permanent sources
of fresh water anywhere on its surface,
there are limited quantities of
groundwater beneath its surface that are
roughly divided into two different kinds
of groundwater. Perched aquifers in the
western parts of Malta that are
geographically situated higher up than
sea level, and lower elevated sea level
aquifers. Historically, the more highly
elevated perched aquifers had more
limited supplies of groundwater, but
their shallower depth than the sea level
aquifers made them relatively easier to
reach. Nonetheless, because rainfall is
scant and largely seasonal in Malta, the
availability of water was always a
chronic issue on the islands until the
modern era. After the Ottomans laid
siege to Malta and failed to capture it
in 1565,
the Knights of St. John began the
construction of the fortified city of
Valletta on that peninsula that
separates the Grand Harbor from the
Marsamxett Harbor on the island.
Well aware of the lack of water in this
area, however, and nervous about another
siege, the Knights mandated that every
single home and building in Valletta
needed to have a well or cistern, while
gardens were explicitly forbidden in
order to conserve even more water. After
the city continued growing and the
Knights realized that rainwater and
limited groundwater wasn't going to be
enough to sustain it, they began
building Malta's first major aqueduct in
1610.
When it was finished in 1615, the
aqueduct began delivering water to
Valletta from a spring up on higher
ground about 27 km away that was enough
to supply all of the city's freshwater
needs until the 19th century, when the
population began growing dramatically.
After the British took over Malta's
political affairs in 1800, they
eventually introduced the island's first
motorized pumps and were the first ones
to actually exploit the island's larger
and deeper sea-level aquifers in an
organized manner. The British introduced
industrial water storage and
exploitation to the islands with huge
underground reservoirs, pumping
stations, and pipelines. They
constructed a series of small dams in
one of the valleys of Malta to collect
rainfall in a reservoir called the
Chadwick Lakes. And they even
experimented with a very early form of
seawater desalination in Malta all the
way back in the 1880s that attempted to
boil seawater and condense the resulting
vapor. While the technology worked at
the time, it was also far too energy
intensive to ever be economically
viable. The dream was there to
eventually take advantage of the fact
that Malta was literally surrounded by
water, just the wrong kind of water, but
it wouldn't become economically viable
until the advent of modern reverse
osmosis desalination nearly a century
later in the 1960s.
During the Second World War between 1940
and 1942, when Malta was besieged by the
Axis powers, the island came dangerously
close to simply running out of water
entirely.
The Axis bombing campaign of Malta
deliberately targeted the island's
pumping stations, water mains,
electricity infrastructure, and
reservoirs. And by early 1941, the
island's water service had already been
put out of action. Water began to be
rationed, but water delivery on Malta
was forced to improvise with water carts
and tanks hidden beneath rocks for
protection. Even though the Axis siege
was broken by the Allies over the summer
of 1942, it showed how vulnerable Malta
still was to water supply issues even in
the 20th century.
>> [music]
>> And the situation would arguably get
even worse just a few decades later in
the late 1970s and early 1980s.
Following the end of the Second World
War, rapid population growth, economic
development, plumbing, tourism, and
agriculture all caused water consumption
in Malta to skyrocket.
For a few decades, Malta dealt with this
simply by pumping up more of its ground
water. But like all other aquifers
around the world, they weren't
bottomless.
The aquifers beneath Malta are formed
through decades of rainfall slowly
percolating beneath the surface, and
they can't be replenished very quickly.
If fresh water gets removed from the
aquifers faster than rainfall can
replenish it, salty sea water lying
beneath the fresh water layer will start
to infiltrate it, which is exactly what
started happening in Malta by the late
1970s.
Groundwater production began to be
forced to slow down, and water rationing
once again returned back to Malta.
The natural water supply on Malta had
reached its maximum demand capacity. And
in order to grow any further, the island
needed a brand new source of water to
add to its supply mix. And luckily for
Malta, this was about at the exact same
time the reverse osmosis desalination
was starting to become really
economically feasible.
Rather than boiling sea water and
condensing the vapor, reverse osmosis
forces the water under enormous pressure
through membranes that allow water
molecules to pass through while
rejecting dissolved solids. In 1983,
Malta finally opened what was at the
time the largest reverse osmosis plant
in the world at Għar Lapsi. And with it,
the island initiated a revolution in its
water supply. For the first time in
Malta's history, the amount of available
potable water wasn't strictly defined by
the island's rainfall. Malta was finally
able to connect itself to an
inexhaustible raw water reservoir, the
Mediterranean Sea itself. And additional
reverse osmosis plants quickly followed.
Today, roughly 70% of Malta's water
supply comes through reverse osmosis
desalination, while the remaining 30%
still comes up from groundwater, which
makes Malta by far the most
desalination-dependent country in Europe
today, and the most
desalination-dependent anywhere in the
world outside of the Middle East. And
today, much like throughout Malta's
history, there are still fears that the
islands are approaching the point of
overpopulation.
We now know from archaeological evidence
that Malta has been inhabited since at
least around 6500 BC. But we also know
that Malta appears to have been abruptly
abandoned for decades sometime around
2500 BC, perhaps because of water supply
issues.
The next time that Malta appears to have
been largely abandoned in the historical
record was after the Arab conquest of
the islands in 870 AD, which was such a
devastating event that the islands
remained practically uninhabited for
nearly the next 180 years until 1048,
when they were resettled again by other
Arabs who came from Sicily, which is why
the Maltese language today is a Semitic
language that's closely related to
Arabic and somewhat mutually
intelligible with the Arabic that's
still spoken today in Tunisia and Libya.
Throughout most of Malta's history,
before and after both of these periods
of abandonment, the population was never
remotely as large as it's become today.
Just a little more than 500 years ago in
the 15th century, Malta's population
wasn't even more than 20,000 people. And
yet its rulers still believed at that
time that it was probably too many.
The last time in Malta's history that
the islands produced a surplus of wheat
and barley was all the way back sometime
around 1437.
From 1440 onwards, and even more so
after 1480, Malta began importing larger
and larger amounts of food from beyond
the islands in order to sustain
themselves, especially from nearby
Sicily, which led to widespread concerns
of overpopulation on the islands.
Before the Knights of St. John took
charge of Malta in 1530, they conducted
a commission which reported that Malta
was a sterile, arid, rocky island that
couldn't provide enough food for even
its own population for any more than
just 4 months out of the year. By 1632,
when the Knights conducted a census in
Malta to determine how much food they
needed to import from Sicily, they
discovered that the island's population
by then stood at a little more than
45,000 people, more than double the
number since they had arrived to the
islands a century earlier. Nearly three
centuries later, when the British
conducted their own census in Malta in
1901, they found that the population had
climbed to more than 184,000
people, which the British government
believed was unsustainable and which
also gave Malta the highest population
density anywhere in the world at the
time.
In 1964, when Malta gained its
independence from Britain, the new
Maltese government explicitly identified
overpopulation as one of the new
country's biggest problems to deal with,
along with a lack of job and wealth
creation to provide a good enough life
for the island's residents.
Between 1948 and 1967, as Malta's
economy stagnated and overpopulation
pressures intensified, nearly a third of
the entire island's population simply
packed up their bags and left to find
better economic opportunities elsewhere,
lending Malta a historical legacy of an
immigrating nation, much like Ireland.
Nonetheless, by the turn of the 21st
century, Malta's population had swelled
to roughly 400,000 people. And in only
the 26 years since then, it swelled even
further to more than 588,000
people. And it's projected to reach more
than 630,000
people by the end of this decade in
2030.
By that point, Malta's population
density will be approaching 2,000 people
per square kilometer. And it'll likely
surpass Bahrain's population density to
become the second most densely populated
non-microstate country in the world,
only behind Singapore.
And what's truly remarkable is the local
indigenous Maltese people are not the
ones who've been driving any of this
population growth at all. Their birth
rate has been continually collapsing for
decades now,
>> [music]
>> to the point where it's now among the
absolute lowest in the world today. The
last time that Malta's fertility rate
was at the replacement level of 2.1
children per woman was all the way back
in 1975.
And it's declined every single decade
since then, to the point where currently
stands at just 1.06
children per woman today, which is the
lowest birth rate in Europe outside of
Ukraine and Vatican City, and the
seventh lowest measured in the world.
And it's even worse for indigenous
Maltese women whose own fertility rate
has fallen all the way to just 0.7
children per woman right now, which is
even lower than the lowest fertility
rate in the world in South Korea, which
currently stands at 0.76 children per
woman. And yet, Malta is also Europe's
fastest growing country at the same
time, having gained 47% in its
population just since the start [music]
of the century in 2000.
And that's because Malta's modern
population explosion has been entirely
driven by immigration from abroad rather
than by local births.
As recently as 2015, only 10% of Malta's
population were born abroad outside of
the islands. But then, within just 10
years by 2025, that ratio had more than
tripled to roughly 31% of Malta's
population be foreign-born, which is now
the highest ratio of any country in
Europe other than microstates and
Luxembourg. And more are still coming
with every passing year. Just between
the summers of 2025 and 2026 alone,
Malta's population grew by 2.4%
year over year. By far the highest
growth rate seen anywhere on the
European continent that was nearly
double the next highest growth rate of
1.3% that was seen in Luxembourg.
[music]
As far back as 2014, Malta's government
spoke openly about emulating the
economic growth model of Dubai on the
islands by encouraging unprecedented
immigration from abroad. And as recently
as June of 2023, Malta's finance
minister stated plainly that the
country's population should increase to
800,000 strong by 2040.
By 2050, if current projections hold, it
has been estimated that two out of every
three workers in Malta will be
foreign-born.
People from all walks of life and from
all around the world are attracted to
move to Malta for a variety of reasons.
The country has been a part of the EU
since 2004, which opened up relatively
easy migration to Malta from the rest of
the EU for people seeking warmer
weather, lower taxes, and a population
that is overwhelmingly fluent in English
because of the long history of British
colonial rule. Malta's top personal
income tax rate tops out at just 35%,
which isn't the lowest rate in the EU,
but it's still significantly lower than
in countries like Germany, France,
Spain, the Netherlands, Belgium, or
Sweden, which in addition to the warm
climate and the English language
proficiency has made it an attractive
place to relocate to for mobile
high-income individuals from these other
countries. It's also increasingly an
attractive place for internationally
mobile foreign companies to relocate to,
as well, because of Malta's unique
corporate tax structure. Malta
officially charges a relatively high 35%
corporate tax rate, but there's a major
loophole built in where active trading
profits that are distributed to a
holding company allow for a 6/7 refund
of all the corporate tax paid. This
means that in reality, the final net
corporate tax rate the companies
actually end up paying in Malta is only
5%, a fraction of most other countries.
For example, in the UK, the corporate
tax rate is a firm 25% without any
loopholes like this, which means that a
UK-based company that relocates to Malta
can save huge amounts of money on their
corporate tax bill, and they'll also be
in a much warmer, sunnier country where
everybody still speaks English anyway.
In 2025, Sky Bet, which used to be a
major UK-based online gambling company,
made headlines when they relocated their
headquarters to Malta for exactly these
reasons, and they'll almost certainly
not be the last large UK company to do
so.
The population of millionaires in Malta
grew by an astonishing 74% over just 10
years between 2013 to 2023 for all of
these reasons. But normal everyday
people are moving to Malta in large
numbers as well in search of work in the
booming construction, hospitality, and
tourism industries. Tourism, especially,
is one of the largest industries and
economic drivers in Malta that has been
continually growing larger and larger
across the 21st century, which
contributes to the island's feeling even
more densely populated than their raw
population numbers alone would suggest.
As recently as 2000, Malta only received
about 1.2 million tourists throughout
the year. But only a quarter of a
century later in 2025, Malta received
more than 4 million tourists, nearly
quadruple the number who had visited
back in 2000.
Based on a per capita metric of foreign
tourist nights spent per 1,000
residents, Malta is now the third most
heavily visited non-microstate country
in Europe, remaining only just barely
behind Croatia and Iceland.
During the peak of the summer travel
season, Malta's actual population
includes roughly 110,000
tourists at any given time, which means
that Malta's summertime population
already swells to as many as 700,000
people when all of the tourists are
included as well, which only makes Malta
feel even more dense.
Tourism and hospitality, along with the
low taxes that are attracting foreign
companies and millionaires, make up a
substantial part of the Maltese economy
today, and they're the major driver of
the island's explosive population growth
during the 21st century as well. But
they're also causing Malta's cost of
living to explode at the same time, and
it's arguably harming the quality of
life for the average local Maltese
person, too.
The average asking price for an
apartment in Malta has soared to 414,000
euros as of 2026,
almost 10% higher than it was just the
year previously in 2025, and roughly 16
times the average Maltese annual income.
For reference, in the US, the price of
an average house is only about 3 and 1/2
times the average American annual
income. So, the housing affordability
crisis in Malta is about 4 and 1/2 times
worse than it is in America. And then,
there's the matter of traffic and
congestion with all of these people and
tourists to consider in Malta as well.
You might expect that the most densely
populated country in Europe with more
than four times the density of the
Netherlands would have a robust public
transportation and metro system. But,
Malta, in fact, doesn't even have a
single operational railway or metro at
all. All public transportation on the
islands is conducted entirely by bus and
ferry, and most people just drive
everywhere themselves. Practically all
transportation in Malta shares the exact
same road network, which makes Malta
feel extremely congested with traffic
basically all of the time. There are
about 440,000
motor vehicles that are currently
registered in Malta, which gives it one
of the highest densities of vehicles
anywhere on the planet. Malta averages
1,392
motor vehicles per square kilometer
right now, which is even more than
Singapore, [music]
a literal city-state which averages
1,338
motor vehicles per square kilometer.
As a result, what was once a calm,
peaceful island in the Mediterranean
appears to increasingly look more and
more like a giant car park these days.
And in addition to the traffic and the
rising housing prices, many Maltese
increasingly fear the loss of their
identity that could accompany all of
this immigration as well. The Maltese
language itself is an incredibly unique
gem of a language that is entirely a
product of these islands' unique
history. It is the only Semitic language
in the world that is written in the
Latin alphabet. Its speakers invoke the
word Allah whenever they pray to God
while being an overwhelmingly Roman
Catholic people. It is still somewhat
mutually intelligible with Arabic
speakers in nearby Tunisia and Libya,
and it is the only Semitic language that
is indigenous in the EU. The Maltese,
understandably, desire to safeguard the
unique heritage of their language. But
how much can they manage to do that in
this era of globalization, where the
local indigenous Maltese fertility rate
is already among the lowest in the world
because of the island's cost of living
crisis, [music] where Malta's population
is already nearly 1/3 foreign-born and
might reach more than 40% foreign-born
by 2050,
and on top of all of the millions of
non-Maltese speaking tourists who visit
the islands every year? Malta's economy
and population both might well continue
growing substantially further during the
21st century. But to what end? Does the
average Maltese person experience a
better quality of life today with all of
the increased density and the larger
economy than their parents or their
grandparents did? The answer to that
question is very far from clear, as is
the direction of Malta's future.
One of the most concerning things about
living here right now is that there were
pretty weak data privacy laws and a ton
of personal data that gets put out into
the public record, frequently by local,
state, and federal governments
themselves. It's always actually been
like that here, and it wasn't ever
really a huge problem before the advent
of the internet. But these days, it
means that people are able to turn a
profit off of making it easier for other
people to get your personal information,
and they do. They're called people
sites, and if you want to see for
yourself, just search your name and
address or phone number, and you'll
probably come across a bunch of these
sites that list at least some of your
personal information. But you also have
the power to change this. You have the
legal right to request that your
personal data is removed from each and
every one of these sites. The biggest
problem is that it takes forever to
actually do that. They make it as hard
as possible, and you have to do it
individually over and over again for
every single one of the endless sites
that have it. But that's a problem
video's sponsor, Incogni, fixes. They'll
do this entire process for you on your
behalf. They constantly search for the
internet for any of your personal data
that's out there, and they'll go through
the whole process of taking it all down,
including handling any and all
rejections. Letting Incogni handle all
of this for you is not only great for
your peace of mind, but it can also
really help cut down on obnoxious spam
calls and emails, since it's these very
same services that sell your data in
bulk.
I've been a natural customer of Incogni
for years now, so I knew that it really
works. And I found the cost to be very
well worth it. And it'll be even more
worth it for you because Incogni is
offering you 60% off of their annual
plan when you click the button here on
screen right now, or when you go to
incogni.com/reallifelore
or follow the link that's down below in
the description and use code
reallifelore. It's a great way to help
support my channel and the journalism
that I'm trying to do here as well. And
as always, thank you so much for
watching.